{
  "categories": [],
  "description": " Fill the blanks in the names of these movies. ",
  "difficulty": -1,
  "questions": [{
    "answer": "Furious",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "The Fast and The _______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Beauty",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "______ and the Beast"
  }, {
    "answer": "Dumber",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "Dumb & ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Pride",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "_____ & Prejudice"
  }, {
    "answer": "Bonnie",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "______ and Clyde"
  }, {
    "answer": "Tramp",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "Lady and the _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Demons",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "Angels & ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Hutch",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "Starsky & _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Louise",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "Thelma & ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Screaming",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "Kicking & _________"
  }, {
    "answer": "Confused",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "Dazed and ________"
  }, {
    "answer": "Frog",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "The Princess & the ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Baby",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "3 Men and a ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Four Weddings",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "____ ________ & a Funeral"
  }, {
    "answer": "Sundance Kid",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "Butch Cassidy and the ________ ___"
  }, {
    "answer": "Monty Python",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "_____ ______ and the Holy Grail"
  }, {
    "answer": "Cowboys",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "_______ & Aliens"
  }, {
    "answer": "Gentleman",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "An Officer & a _________"
  }, {
    "answer": "Julie",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "_____ & Julia"
  }, {
    "answer": "Bandit",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "Smokey and the ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Clear",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "_____ and Present Danger"
  }, {
    "answer": "Stand",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "_____ and Deliver"
  }, {
    "answer": "Josie",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "_____ and the Pussycats"
  }, {
    "answer": "Dead",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "The Quick & the ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Good Luck",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "____ Night, and Good ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Harry",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "_____ & the Hendersons"
  }, {
    "answer": "Benny",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "_____ & Joon"
  }, {
    "answer": "Harold",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "______ & Maude"
  }, {
    "answer": "Arsenic",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "_______ and Old Lace"
  }, {
    "answer": "Whale",
    "category": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "The Squid and the _____"
  }],
  "quizLength": 30,
  "title": "'And Something' Movie Titles",
  "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/and-something-movie-titles-quiz.php"
}